classicindustries.com 2018-02-01

# Classic Industries - Company Policies Category

## Classic Industries® Customer Privacy Statement:

Classic Industries® is committed to protecting the privacy of our customers as well as the online shopping experience. Classic Industries® utilizes the information we collect from our customers to process orders and to ensure the most secure online shopping experience. Please read the following as it outlines how your information is collected, protected, and how it is used. 

## Collection and Use of Information:

When submitting your personal information to Classic Industries® we collect your name, address, telephone number, credit card information (orders only), and e-mail address. We use this information to process your orders and to contact you with questions concerning the products you ordered. The information we collect will not be sold or shared with any other company. On occasion, however, Classic Industries® may e-mail new product releases, notifications of changes to our web site or special offers that may be of interest. If you do not want to receive these e-mails please [click here to unsubscribe](http://www.pages01.net/classicindustriesinc/OptOut/OptOut) to our e-mail list. Information sent to Classic Industries® utilizing the contact information page or comment page is used only for correspondence with you regarding the information on file. 

## Google Analytics Data Policy:

Classic Industries® uses Google Analytics software to track the performance of certain web pages and forms on our site. To learn more about how this information is collected and recorded by Google, [follow this link](https://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/learn/privacy.html). 

## Protecting Your Information:

Classic Industries® maintains security measures to protect your personal information stored in our systems. All user information is stored on secure networks that are only accessible by a limited number of employees who have agreed to comply with company policy on privacy and security. For Information on site security and our third party participants please visit [www.securitymetrics.com](http://www.securitymetrics.com/). 

## About SSL Certificates:

All registration and order information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and is encrypted by the software before the information is sent across the Internet. VeriSign, Inc has certified classicindustries.com is a secure network for e-commerce transactions. Please be sure that your browser is SSL-enabled. For optimum security and to view the website the way it was intended, you should always upgrade your browser software to the latest version. 

## Cookies and Other Data Information:

Classic Industries® uses cookie technology to store information on your computer system. This technology does not record any identifying information or personal data about our customers. The information stored helps us identify what parts of our website you have visited and determine what products to offer in the future. Classic Industries® collects information to monitor traffic patterns and site usage to help us improve the design and effectiveness of our site. We may provide statistical information about our customers to reputable third party vendors for email marketing, and/or other advertising purposes to provide our customers with the most relevant information possible. This data does not contain any identifying personal information about our customers. 

## Links to Other Relevant Sites:

Our web site may contain links to other automotive based sites to help provide useful information to our customers across the globe. These sites may require you to input information for their data collection purposes. These sites should have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of Classic Industries®. Classic Industries® has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions and is not responsible for the privacy practice or the content of such web sites. 

## Classic Industries® Pricing:

While we try to ensure accuracy, we reserve the right to correct any errors in pricing or descriptions, and to cancel or refuse to accept any order based on an incorrect price or description. Such corrections may be made even after an order is accepted. Customers will be notified of any price or description issues. 

## Classic Industries® Policy:

Classic Industries® maintains the rights to change, update, or modify this policy statement at any time. All changes will be reflected on this page and it is the dealers responsibility to review this page and to be aware of any changes to the privacy policy. Classic Industries® respects your privacy and will never ask for personal information in an email advertisement or sell your email address to a third party. 

Thank you for taking the time to read our privacy statement. If you have any questions or concerns please contact us.
